all right so this is queerness part two
part of what happens when I encounter
people that were non-binary especially
this is my language females that are
non-binary was that there was this I was
attracted to them it's put it bluntly I
was definitely attracted to them and I
didn't know whether it was because I
wanted to be them or I wanted to be with
them and it became to the point where it
doesn't matter it's both of those things
it can be both but I had to break from
this heteronormative that masculine not
just with feminine and I realized how
much of my life as a heterosexual woman
I was trying to be something to attract
a heterosexual man and when I came to
the realization I was queer and
attracted to different genders I gave
that up I was like I'm not gonna be
anything besides Who I am and whoever
that attracts great and whoever it
doesn't whoever it turns off even better
I love my coming-out story to myself
because I don't live in closets I can't
do closet so once I know I'm something
everybody knows I'm something
what Sonny was autistic everyone else I
want to say was I was queer everyone I
was a queer but I was watching orange is
the new black and there was this really
beautiful romantic scene between two of
the women in it I was like oh do I get
to go to prison and have a girlfriend
like you know you are allowed to have a
girlfriend not go to prison like that's
about the queerest thought somebody
could have you're queer and and then I
was out I was out to myself and I
eventually came out to my family
not eventually just like the next time I
talked to them I was basically like
remember what I came out and like you
haven't tell me I was like oh right now
I guess right now my siblings kind of
already knew I was he I was gay before I
did which probably made it last longer
me not knowing because it was like this
I'm not what do you mean no I'm not
aspect to it but it also I
had been critical of one of my family
members who came out later in life
because he's kind of asexual and I was
like yeah okay so now you're gonna not
date men like you don't eat you don't
know date women I had a roommate at one
point in time who was both poly and
asexual and I was like you can't be both
of those things and this is where my
karma always comes into play because
whenever I'm critical of someone else
again becomes my life and so I am both
coming came out as queer late like
mid-30s and I am both demisexual which
is on the asexual spectrum and I think
what be Paulie - and I have not in any
way actually like physically in the real
world explored those things because of
my disability and being a single mom I
keep to myself but there isn't enough of
an incentive as a demisexual to go out
I'm perfectly happy being single and I
would love a partner both of those
things are simultaneously my body and I
am kind of non-binary gender with like
the masculine feminine I'm like I'm
neither I'm both I don't know you asked
me on the day me and I'm attracted to
people who are also
non-binary mainly and then also
masculine and I'm not really attracted
to the feminine but sometimes I am
sometimes it's just like who shows up
and it's their energy there's a cup
handful of people who are feminine
enough like I love you you're so awesome
and not in a way that I love my friends
who are also awesome and it's just that
it's just like in the moment not needing
it to be anything because I came from a
very strong like this is how it is these
are the rules in fact there were rules
that because I wasn't that I couldn't be
gay because yet I didn't have those same
rules for my heterosexuality and they
applied to both he's like oh wait no no
that doesn't make any sense
and so I both identify as queer and I
have never kissed a girl and I don't
know if I well I don't know if that if I
need to get healthy again if I need to
not have that be stressful in order to
do it I'm just taking it as it goes
and enjoying as I explained when I came
out like my imaginary boyfriend has been
replaced by imaginary girlfriend or an
imaginary partner like that's just how
it goes and that like that was part of
what I was critical about with other
people isn't like you can't if you
haven't actually done stuff come on like
no it's a it's an inner world if I was
on a deserted island and came to those
realizations it wouldn't make it less
real and I'm a little bit on a deserted
island in my own life at the moment
online dating doesn't work for me but I
can imagine a online dating that would
work and so when we create that I might
use it and until then I'm kind of good
I'm good being me and exploring it I was
at calmness and not forcing it but this
was part two of queerness